It's reading and baseball.
Those are the two things I care about because I believe in those two things, bettering Black neighborhoods.
Baseball?
Yes, absolutely.
Please expound.
Baseball teaches you failure.
Baseball is a game of failure.
And Black people need to learn failure?
You need to learn how to do it.
I think we got that down pat.
I don't know, bro.
I got to think.
That's one thing we could teach.
Yeah, it's patience.
It's strategy.
It's waiting for the right moment to make your move.
You're alone, but you're part of a bigger ecosystem.
It's a team sport, but it's really a bunch of people.
Individually doing well within the?
Within their space to help the community.
The community.
Your job is just first base.
Don't worry about second.
Don't worry about left field.
Because second and left field are worrying about second and left field.
Correct.
And you can trust that.
But just do what you're supposed to do when it's your time to do something, but do exactly what you're supposed to do.